redevolution.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy

Red Evolution is committed to protecting the privacy of our website users.  In this policy we set how we will deal with your personal details.

Any information collected and stored, including cookies, will be of the following kind:

  * Your visits and use of our website.
  * Information provided for the use of registering and/or subscribing to our website service.
  * Information provided for business purposes including quotes, analysis and reviews etc
  * Contact details provided in the course of downloading information

**Website Visits**

We may collect information about your visits to our website such as IP address, location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. This information may be used to improve our website's usability and for general marketing purposes. This data is not personally identifiable.

**Cookies are used on this website.**

Some of the services we use such as Google Analytics, Clicky Analytics and addThis set cookies to allow us to gather anonymous data about your usage of our website.

A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser and stored in the browser.  The file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page form the server.  This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may send a cookie which may be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. The information we obtain from the cookie could be used to improve the website’s usability and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognise your computer when you visit our website, and to personalise our website for you.

Browsers usually will allow you to refuse cookies but this could have a negative impact on the usability of many websites.

**Albacross Lead Generation Data**

We also process personal data on the behalf of Albacross Nordic AB ("Albacross").

Information collected from cookies set in your device that qualify as personal data will be processed by Albacross, a company offering lead identification and ad targeting services with offices in Stockholm and Krakow. Please see below for full contact details.

The purpose for the processing of the personal data is that it enables Albacross to improve a service rendered to us and our website (a "Lead Generation" service), by adding data to their database about companies.

The data that is collected and used by Albacross to achieve this purpose is information about the IP-address from which you visited our website, and technical information that enables Albacross to tell apart different visitors from the same IP-address. Albacross stores the domain from form input in order to correlate the IP-address with your employer.

You may at any time withdraw your consent to this processing. Such withdrawal may be made either by contacting us, or by contacting Albacross directly.

Albacross Nordic AB  
Kungsgatan 26  
111 35 Stockholm, Sweden  
www.albacross.com - contact@albacross.com

**Using your personal data**

Personal data submitted on this website could be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in any relevant parts of the website.

Our lawful bases for processing your personal data are: contract (e.g. for the purposes of providing a quote or requested information in order to do business with you) or consent (e.g. you provide your contact details in order to request information from us).

In addition to the uses already identified we may use your personal information to:

Improve your browsing experience by personalising the website.

Send marketing communications, if you have chosen to receive them.

Provide other companies with statistical information about our users; however, this information will not be used to identify an individual user.

We will not provide any personal information to a third party unless you have given your permission.

**Marketing**

If you have consented to receive marketing communications from us you can opt out at any time. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please email info@redevolution.com

**Other Disclosures**

In addition to disclosures already discussed we may need to disclose the following information:

Where a country’s legal system requires us to disclose your personal information.

In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings.

In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights. (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk)

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

**International data transfers**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed by third party data processing companies to enable us to provide you with a suitable service. We only deal with reputable data processors and we are confident that your data is stored securely in accordance with data protection best practice.

If you are in the European Union, information which you provide may be transferred to and processed in countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Union. When you provide personal information, you expressly agree to such transfers.

**Security of your personal data**

We will take reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers or on third party secure servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted.

**Data retention**

All data relating to non-customers who have been inactive for more than six months will be deleted from our contact records. Inactive means that they have not opened any email or visited our website during that time period. Customer records will be held for longer in accordance with financial and business requirements. 

**Policy amendments**

We may occasionally update this privacy policy by posting a new version on our website. It is in your interest to check this page regularly to ensure you are comfortable with any changes made.

**Third party websites**

Our website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of any third party websites.

**Your Rights**

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you or transfer it to another IT environment. Data will be provided as a CSV file.

You can request us not to use any of your personal details, or to update, change or delete them. You can instruct us to make changes or remove your personal data by emailing us at info@redevolution.com. All requests will be acted on and responded to within 21 days. All complaints about data usage should also be sent to [info@redevolution.com](mailto:info@redevolution.com).

This policy together with our website terms and conditions constitutes the entire agreement between you and us in relation to your use of our website, and supersedes all previous agreements in respect of your use of this website.

**Contact us**

If you need any more information, please contact us at Red Evolution Ltd [info@redevolution.com](mailto:info@redevolution.com).
